

LUNA SARMIENTO

FULL STACK WEB
DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hi! My name is Luna, I'm 22 and I love to code websites. The thing that I like most about this field is the fact that it allows me to be creative while using my logical thinking skills. Thanks to my previous experiences, I'm really good at working in teams and I'm also very patient.

TECH SKILLS

- HTML 5
- TypeScript
- CSS 3
- Express
- JavaScript
- GitHub
- React.js
- MongoDb
- Node.js
- PostgreSQL

CONTACTS

Address: Via Enzo Ferrari 12 Bologna, Italy

- Iunisel99@gmail.com
- luna-sarmiento.vercel.app/



github.com/lunisel



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Waitress

La Torinese 1888 | October 2019 - July 2020

- Serving tables
- Making coffee and other drinks
- Clean after night shifts
- Interact with customers and handle their complaints if they had any.

English Tutor

EDUCO Italia | February 2019 - June 2019

- Help the English teacher during the afternoon lessons, with children from 6 to 10 years old.
- Play and interact with them and manage the most difficult ones, taking them outside to calm them down if necessary



EDUCATION

Strive School

Graduated from Full Stack batch | May 2021 - November 2021

1200+ hours of coding

20+ team and individual projects, developed in a fully remote and international environment.

Liceo Artistico F.Arcangeli

High school diploma | 2013 - 2018

- Two years exploring various types of artistic expressions including painting and sculpture
- Three years in the audiovisual / multimedia field exploring subjects such as photography, photo editing and video design in each step (from storyboard to practical realization)



HOBBIES

In my free time I like to play the guitar and sing, I love all artistic expressions and I enjoy drawing, photographing my friends, taking walks in nature and watching movies and TV series. I also like traveling, meeting people and living new experiences.